Guide to the Records of the Office of the University Architect/Joseph J. Roberto Collection RG.11.4
New York University Archives
- Series XVI: Oversize
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Windows and Doorways -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Technology I -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Technology I -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Technology II -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Technology II -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Gould Hall Residence Hall -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Buildings -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Buildings -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kayburn Textile Building -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Campus Shots -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - University Heights Campus Shots -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Nichols Hall, University Heights -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Bliss Hall, University Heights -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - South Building, Washington Square College -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Model of Proposed Building -- Image, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Proposed Administration Offices -- Plans, 1960 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Proposed Administration Offices, Alternative Site #1 -- Plans, 1960 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Proposed Administration Offices, Landscape -- Plans, 1960 (Drawer RA 5)
  - General Classroom Building, Basement -- Plans, 1960 (Drawer RA 5)
  - General Classroom Building, 1st Floor -- Plans, 1960 (Drawer RA 5)
  - General Classroom Building, 3rd Floor -- Plans, 1960 (Drawer RA 5)
  - General Classroom Building, 4th Floor -- Plans, 1960 (Drawer RA 5)
  - General Classroom Building, 6th Floor -- Plans, 1960 (Drawer RA 5)
  - General Classroom Building, 7th Floor -- Plans, 1960 (Drawer RA 5)
  - View from Parlor of Washington Square North Homes-- Drawing, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Washignton Square Park, Looking Southwest -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - View from Parlor of Washington Square North Homes -- Drawings, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - View from Parlor of Washington Square North Homes -- Drawings, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - View from Parlor of Washington Square North Homes -- Drawings, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - View from Parlor of Washington Square North Homes -- Drawings, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - View from Parlor of Washington Square North Homes -- Drawings, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - View from Parlor of Washington Square North Homes -- Drawings, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - View from Parlor of Washington Square North Homes -- Drawings, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - View from Parlor of Washington Square North Homes -- Drawings, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - View from Parlor of Washington Square North Homes -- Drawings, 1967 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Deutches Haus -- Plans, 1967 (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Main Building, Washington Square College, Exterior -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kimmell Center, 2nd Floor Layout -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 2nd Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, Elevations -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 8th Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 8th Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 3rd Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 3rd Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 3rd Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 3rd Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 1st Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 1st Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 4th Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 4th Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 5th Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, 6th Floor -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, Basement -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, Basement -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, Basement -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Loeb Student Center, Alternate Site -- Plans, 1955 (Drawer RA 5)
  - Portfolio of Kevorkian Center -- Plans/Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Tau Epsilon Phi House -- Drawing, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Medical Center, Schwartz Hall -- Sketch, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Portfolio of La Maison Francaise -- Plans/Drawings, 1977 (Folder 6, Folder 7)
  - Folder of SENAP Material for Children's School, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Portfolio of Master Plan, University Heights Map & NYU Camp, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Book -- Plan for NYC, 1: Critical Issues, 1969 (Box 53)
  - Book -- Plan for NYC, 4: Manhattan, 1969 (Box 53)
  - Comprehensive Plan for University Heights -- Images/Plans/Drawings/Maps, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Floorplan of home, MacDougal & 4th, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Floorplan of home, MacDougal & 4th, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - School of Aviation Research Center -- Plans, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Jewish Center -- Plans/Sketches, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Sketch by J. Roberto, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Economic Department Offices -- Plans, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - School of the Arts, Fillmore East -- Plans (roll), undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Granite Center Piece, Gould Plaza, Washington Square Campus, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Lettering for School of Education, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - Kevorkian Center Moulding -- Wood, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - 707 Broadway -- Plans, undated (Drawer RA 5)
  - NYU 1963, Heights Campus -- Images (Drawer RA 5)
  - Milton F. Kirchman v. Joseph J. Roberto, Exibitions IA-IG on Deutches Haus, 1969-1977 (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Kevorkian Center photos, 1967-1976 (Box Shared University Archives 091, Folder 5)
- Series XVII: Blueprints
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements Note
  The blueprints in Box 40 are tightly folded and inaccessible to researchers.
  - Subseries I: WASHINGTON SQUARE CAMPUS
    - School of the Arts -- Plans, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Bleeker St Properties -- Plans, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - 693 Broadway -- Plans, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - 707 Broadway -- Plans, 1962-1963 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - 707 Broadway -- Plans, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - 707 Broadway -- Plans, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - 707 Broadway -- Plans, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - 707 Broadway -- Plans, 1966-1970 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Brown Building -- Plans, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Brown Building -- Plans, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Brown Building -- Plans, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Brown Building -- Plans, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Brown Building -- Plans, 1962-1964 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Brown Building -- Plans, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Brown Building -- Plans, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Brown Building -- Plans, 1964-1966 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Catholic Center -- Plans, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Commerce Building -- Plans, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans, 1958-1971 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Deutches Haus Building -- Plans Sketches, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - School of Education -- Plans, 1937-1961 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - School of Education -- Plans, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - School of Education -- Plans, 1962-1966 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - School of Education -- Plans, 1966-1972 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - E8th St and University Place -- Plans, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Experimental School for Children -- Plans, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Farkas Hall -- Plans, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - 545 Fith Ave -- Plans, 1968-1972 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Grace Church -- Plans, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Hayden Hall -- Plans, 1960-1962 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Hayden Hall -- Plans, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Hayden Hall -- Plans, 1962-1969 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Hayden Hall -- Plans, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Judson Block and Residence -- Plans, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Kevorkian Center -- Plans, 1961-1982 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Kevorkian Center -- Plans, 1962-1982 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Kimball Hall -- Plans, 1962-1963 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Kimball Hall -- Plans, 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - La Maison Francaise -- Plans, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Library -- Plans, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Library (Bobst) -- Plans, 1964-1972 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Main Building -- Plans, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Main Building -- Plans, 1961-1963 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Main Building -- Plans, 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Main Building -- Plans, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Maps -- Traffic Studies, Washington Square Area, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Maps -- Washington Square Area, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Maps -- Washington Square Park, 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Maps -- Washington Square Park, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Maps -- Washington Sq. Slum Clearance, 1957-1962 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Reparatory Theater (ANTA) -- Plans, 1962-1964 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Rubin Residence Hall -- Plans, 1964-1966 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Tisch Hall -- Plans, 1967-1968 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - University Place Residence Hall -- Plans, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - University Place Residence Hall -- Plans, 1960-1963 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - 13-19 University Place -- Plans, 1960-1962 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - 13-19 University Place -- Plans, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - 13-19 University Place -- Plans, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - 13-19 University Place -- Plans, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - 13-19 University Place -- Plans, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - 13-19 University Place -- Plans, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - 13-19 University Place -- Plans, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - 13-19 University Place -- Plans, 1963-1965 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - 13-19 University Place -- Plans, 1965-1966 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - 13-19 University Place -- Plans, 1967-1969 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - 13-19 University Place -- Plans, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - 13-19 University Place -- Plans, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Vanderbilt Hall -- Plans, 1961-1965 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Vanderbilt Hall -- Plans, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Vanderbilt Hall -- Plans, 1968-1978 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Vanderbilt Hall -- Plans, 1968-1978 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, 1959-1962 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Warren Weaver Hall -- Plans, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - 10 Washington Mews -- Plans, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - 14 Washington Mews -- Plans, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - 15 Washington Mews -- Plans, 1962-1966 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - 48 Washington Mews -- Plans, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - 52 Washington Mews -- Plans, 1965-1966 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - 52 Washington Mews -- Plans, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - 4-6 Washington Place -- Plans, 1956-1966 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - 4-6 Washington Place -- Plans, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - 8 Washington Place -- Plans, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - 21 Washington Place -- Plans, 1964-1966 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - 1 Washington Square North -- Plans, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - 3 Washington Square North -- Plans, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - 4 Washington Square North -- Plans, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - 5 Washington Square North -- Plans, 1939-1976 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - 6 Washington Square North -- Plans, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - 21 Washington Square North -- Plans, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Washington Square Village Area -- Plans, 1957-1961 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Washington Square Village Area -- Plans, 1962-1966 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Washington Square Village Area -- Plans, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Washington Square Village Area -- Plans, undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Washington Square Village Area -- Plans, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Washington Square Village Area -- Plans, undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall -- Plans, 1960-1963 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall -- Plans, 1963-1965 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall -- Plans, 1965-1968 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall -- Plans, undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Unidentified Buildings -- Plans, undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Unidentified Buildings -- Plans, undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Unidentified Buildings -- Plans, undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Lettering for Buildings -- Plans, undated (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Subseries II: UNIVERSITY HEIGHTS CAMPUS
    - Bennet Residence Hall -- Plans, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Beryllium & Oceanographic Docking Facility -- Plans, 1961-1962 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Building Plans -- Crow, Lewis, Wickenhoefer, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Building Plans -- Crow, Lewis, Wickenhoefer, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Building Plans -- Kimball & Fiske, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Building Plans -- Day & Klauder, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Building Plans -- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Butler Hall -- Plans, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - NYU Camp, Sterling Forest -- Plans, undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Club -- Plans, undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Gates, University Heights -- Plans, undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Geology Research Lab, Sterling Forest -- Plans, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Gould Hall of Technology, Spectrograph Facility -- Plans, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Gould Library -- Plans, 1962-1965 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Gould Residence Hall -- Plans, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Gould Student Center -- Plans, 1962-1967 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Housing, University Valley -- Plans, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Group Housing #2 -- Plans, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Guggenheim Hall -- Plans, 1962-1964 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Hall of Fame -- Plans, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Havemeyer Annex -- Plans, 1959-1964 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Harlem River Site Aerospace Laboratory -- Plans, 1964-1965 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Landscaping, University Heights -- Plans, 1959-1964 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Language Hall -- Plans, 1960-1964 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - MacCraken Hall -- Plans, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Maps, University Heights & University Valley -- Plans, 1957-1966 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Maps, University Heights & University Valley -- Plans, undated (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - New Hall -- Plans, undated (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Nichols Building -- Plans, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Philosophy Hall -- Plans, 1962-1964 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Sedgwick Ave. Residence Hall -- Plans, 1965-1968 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Technology I Building -- Plans, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Technology II Building -- Plans, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - University Valley/Sterling Forest -- Maps, 1962-1964 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Subseries III: OTHER UNIVERSITY CENTERS
    - Adult Education Building -- Plans, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Dental College -- Plans, 1960-1964 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Dental College -- Plans, 1964-1970 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration (Wall St.) -- Plans, 1962-1963 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Insitute of Fine Arts -- Plans, 1960-1967 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Medical Center -- Plans, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Medical Center -- Plans, 1962-1964 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Medical Center -- Plans, 1964-1973 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Education Building -- Plans, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - South Building -- Plans, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Students Building -- Plans, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Press Building -- Plans, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - East Building -- Plans, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Brown Building -- Plans, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Main Building -- Plans, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Waverly Place -- Plans, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Barney Building -- Plans, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Subseries IV: NON-NYU BUILDINGS
    - Old Merchant's House Museum Operations, undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - New York City Landmarks, undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - New York City Landmarks, undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Dr. Meltzer/Kips Bay Apartments/Doctor's Suites -- Plans, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Dr. Meltzer/Kips Bay Apartments/Doctor's Suites -- Plans, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Dr. Meltzer/Kips Bay Apartments/Doctor's Suites -- Plans, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Dr. Meltzer/Kips Bay Apartments/Doctor's Suites -- Plans, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Whitney Museum -- Plans, undated (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Proposed Bulkhead, Fill, Pier and Dredging -- Plans, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - 219 E 177th St. (James & Carvel Moore) -- Plans, undated (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - National Recreation Association -- Plans, undated (Box 42, Folder 28)